<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>game on LJ-Left Creations Blog</title>
    <link>https://thatisdrtruman.github.io/tags/game/</link>
    <description>Recent content in game on LJ-Left Creations Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>joeliuprimary@gmail.com (Joe Liu)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>joeliuprimary@gmail.com (Joe Liu)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 01:25:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thatisdrtruman.github.io/tags/game/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fillup Status App 1.3</title>
      <link>https://thatisdrtruman.github.io/posts/fillup-status-app-1.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 01:25:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>joeliuprimary@gmail.com (Joe Liu)</author>
      <guid>https://thatisdrtruman.github.io/posts/fillup-status-app-1.2/</guid>
      <description>This is the fourth post to &amp;lsquo;Fillup&amp;rsquo;, to see the first post about it, go here, the second here, or the third To download the APK, go here, iOS coming soon, but now have a browser version: Site for web app
I now added ten checkboxes to mark in your player&amp;rsquo;s inventory. Whether you already have one of the items and/or abilities. And there is a new Coordinate generator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fillup Status Site</title>
      <link>https://thatisdrtruman.github.io/posts/fillup-status-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 23:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>joeliuprimary@gmail.com (Joe Liu)</author>
      <guid>https://thatisdrtruman.github.io/posts/fillup-status-site/</guid>
      <description> Fillup-status-app but in a browser, internet required: Your HP: 20
Roll Moves Roll Coordinates Your coordinates: , Your abilities:
Stomp Block Slide
Teleport Triple Punch Your items:
Lasoo Wall Mine
Spear HP Bottle (Use: +5HP) To download the Android APK, go here, if you&amp;rsquo;re on PC and want to play it offine, save this page as a single file </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fillup Status App 1.1</title>
      <link>https://thatisdrtruman.github.io/posts/fillup-status-app-1.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 16:08:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>joeliuprimary@gmail.com (Joe Liu)</author>
      <guid>https://thatisdrtruman.github.io/posts/fillup-status-app-1.1/</guid>
      <description>UPDATE 01/02/2024: Download now at fillup-status-app-1.2 This is the third post to &amp;lsquo;Fillup&amp;rsquo;, to see the first post about it, go here, the second here To download the APK, go here, iOS coming soon, but now I have a browser version: Site for web app
I now added two EditText boxes to mark in your player&amp;rsquo;s coordinates, bolded the title and slightly condense them features together.
The HP bar (the number changes as you use the slider) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fillup Status App</title>
      <link>https://thatisdrtruman.github.io/posts/fillup-status-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:27:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>joeliuprimary@gmail.com (Joe Liu)</author>
      <guid>https://thatisdrtruman.github.io/posts/fillup-status-app/</guid>
      <description>UPDATE 01/02/2024: Download now at fillup-status-app-1.2 This is the second post to &amp;lsquo;Fillup&amp;rsquo;, to see the first post about it, go here, or here for the third post To download the APK, go here, iOS coming soon, but now, use browser version: Site for web app
I made this app to organise my game better, by allowing players to roll their moves dice and slide their Health Point themselves. So far, only on Android 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bejin Bot</title>
      <link>https://thatisdrtruman.github.io/posts/bejin-bot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 02:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>joeliuprimary@gmail.com (Joe Liu)</author>
      <guid>https://thatisdrtruman.github.io/posts/bejin-bot/</guid>
      <description>FREE DOWNLOAD
WIP (Still need texture and animation and bio) Bejin Bot A robot designed in Blender inspired by a robot from an Australian animator.
Download here
Still deciding how to colour it, and its purpose in a game, art or story.
Name derived from &amp;lsquo;Begin&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;g&amp;rsquo; soften to &amp;lsquo;j&amp;rsquo;, to reference my first character design in Blender.
Other model pics of Bejin Bot: Update pending.
model-download There you are, this version of Bejin Bot is fully copyleft</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sticky Note Cards and Game</title>
      <link>https://thatisdrtruman.github.io/posts/sticky-note-cards-and-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 16:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>joeliuprimary@gmail.com (Joe Liu)</author>
      <guid>https://thatisdrtruman.github.io/posts/sticky-note-cards-and-game/</guid>
      <description>💌👌
or HERE
I always believe regardless of price, something homemade or unbought always has some soul, a priceless item.
Simple to make: make an art with sticky notes and bookmarks, write your message or picture, and cover it with lots of redundant sticky notes for a game.
If you remove the redundant notes correctly, you will get the right picture and message.
If you would like a personalised card in this style, DM me on Linkedin, Facebook, or Tiktok, starting the message with &amp;ldquo;I would like a sticky note card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fillup</title>
      <link>https://thatisdrtruman.github.io/posts/fillup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 20:29:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>joeliuprimary@gmail.com (Joe Liu)</author>
      <guid>https://thatisdrtruman.github.io/posts/fillup/</guid>
      <description>UPDATE 22 Jan 2024: After playing the game with some people and reviewing how to be more organised, I have made a Fillup Status app for players to track their HP and roll the dice themselves for the number of moves. Download it here or on &amp;lsquo;Fillup Status App&amp;rsquo; page. A game I made in July to January 2023-24, now in its testing phase.
The manual and documentation: https://shorturl.at/kuX29
The game layout: The empty playing board All basic items tokens ready to put in the game: All basic ability tokens ready to put in the game: There are 8 different abilities, each has 4 The healthboard: The player decides behind the wall what they want to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grabo</title>
      <link>https://thatisdrtruman.github.io/posts/grabo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 21:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>joeliuprimary@gmail.com (Joe Liu)</author>
      <guid>https://thatisdrtruman.github.io/posts/grabo/</guid>
      <description>In July/August 2023, I worked on a My First Game Jam project called Grabo.
Inspired by Kingdom Hearts III using Unreal Engine 4, I wanted to make an Unreal Engine 5 Game as a general 2D platformer.
Grabo, a beartrap in a 2D platformer who needs to destroy all melty liquid vats. This is written in Unreal Engine 5.2.1 as a 2023 My First Game Jam entry ( https://itch.io/jam/my-first-game-jam-summer-2023 ).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
